Alternatively, we can think, as most mathematicians do,
that these formulas are merely descriptions of certain
pre-existing mathematical structures, and what math really is,
is the set of all of such structures.
But what would the set consisting
of all mathematical structures look like?
It would have to be something very general and very large, such
that we could simulate essentially whatever we want inside of it.
This is where set theory comes in. A set
is perhaps the most basic object we can consider.
I challenge you to try to define a set without
using a synonym of set, like collection, group, class etc.
The axioms of ZFC are a solid attempt to define what a set is.
The origins of set theory date back to
Georg Cantor in the later 19th century.
Cantor was a mathematical platonist who
envisioned an unrestricted and powerful mathematics.